"lang" 
{ 
"Language" "TChinese" 
"Tokens" 
{
	"Prepare for the upcoming battle against the creatures and scout the unfamiliar terrain"	"爲即將到來的與生物的戰鬥做準備，並在陌生的地形上進行偵察"
	"Prevent the teleportation of hellish creatures and destroy all the portals in their lair"	"阻止地獄生物傳送並摧毀他們巢穴中的所有傳送門"
	"The security system has been activated. The doors are locked. We need to find a way to unlock them"	"安全系統已被激活。門是鎖着的。我們需要想辦法解鎖它們。"
	"We managed to unlock the doors and found useful information on the computers. Now, we can move forward"	"我們設法打開了門，並在計算機上找到了有用的信息。現在，我們可以向前邁進了。"
	"Continue working on destroying the portals from which these filthy creatures emerge"	"繼續摧毀這些骯髒生物出現的入口"
	"The door panel leading to the main hall was broken by those creatures. We need to find a way to fix it"	"通往大廳的門板被那些生物打破了。”我們需要想辦法解決它。"
	"Great, we've acquired a welding machine. Now we can try to repair the panel"	"太好了，我們得到了一臺焊槍。現在我們可以嘗試修復面板了。"
	"An identical panel was in the neighboring room. This might come in handy"	"一個相同的面板在鄰近的房間裏。這可能會派上用場。"
	"We'll have to put in some effort to push the panel to the door we need, leading to the main hall"	"我們得花點力氣把門板推到我們需要的那扇門上，那扇門通向大廳。"
	"On the creatures' computer, we found materials about the explosives in the safe, along with the code — 666. However, one of the two buttons that need to be pressed simultaneously is broken"	"在這些生物的電腦上，我們在保險箱裏找到了有關炸藥的資料，還有密碼- 666。但是，需要同時按下的兩個按鈕之一壞了。"
	"Now, we have everything necessary to destroy the main portal in the hall named 'Oblivion' and get out of here"	"現在，我們有了一切必要的東西來摧毀‘湮滅’大廳的主傳送門，然後離開這裏。"
}
}
