"lang" 
{ 
"Language" "English" 
"Tokens" 
{
	"Prepare for the upcoming battle against the creatures and scout the unfamiliar terrain"	"Prepare for the upcoming battle against the creatures and scout the unfamiliar terrain"
	"Prevent the teleportation of hellish creatures and destroy all the portals in their lair"	"Prevent the teleportation of hellish creatures and destroy all the portals in their lair"
	"The security system has been activated. The doors are locked. We need to find a way to unlock them"	"The security system has been activated. The doors are locked. We need to find a way to unlock them"
	"We managed to unlock the doors and found useful information on the computers. Now, we can move forward"	"We managed to unlock the doors and found useful information on the computers. Now, we can move forward"
	"Continue working on destroying the portals from which these filthy creatures emerge"	"Continue working on destroying the portals from which these filthy creatures emerge"
	"The door panel leading to the main hall was broken by those creatures. We need to find a way to fix it"	"The door panel leading to the main hall was broken by those creatures. We need to find a way to fix it"
	"Great, we've acquired a welding machine. Now we can try to repair the panel"	"Great, we've acquired a welding machine. Now we can try to repair the panel"
	"An identical panel was in the neighboring room. This might come in handy"	"An identical panel was in the neighboring room. This might come in handy"
	"We'll have to put in some effort to push the panel to the door we need, leading to the main hall"	"We'll have to put in some effort to push the panel to the door we need, leading to the main hall"
	"On the creatures' computer, we found materials about the explosives in the safe, along with the code — 666. However, one of the two buttons that need to be pressed simultaneously is broken"	"On the creatures' computer, we found materials about the explosives in the safe, along with the code — 666. However, one of the two buttons that need to be pressed simultaneously is broken"
	"Now, we have everything necessary to destroy the main portal in the hall named 'Oblivion' and get out of here"	"Now, we have everything necessary to destroy the main portal in the hall named 'Oblivion' and get out of here"
}
}
