"lang" 
{ 
"Language" "schinese" 
"Tokens" 
{
	"Prepare for the upcoming battle against the creatures and scout the unfamiliar terrain"	"为即将到来的与生物的战斗做准备，并在陌生的地形上进行侦察"
	"Prevent the teleportation of hellish creatures and destroy all the portals in their lair"	"阻止地狱生物传送并摧毁他们巢穴中的所有传送门"
	"The security system has been activated. The doors are locked. We need to find a way to unlock them"	"安全系统已被激活。门是锁着的。我们需要想办法解锁它们。"
	"We managed to unlock the doors and found useful information on the computers. Now, we can move forward"	"我们设法打开了门，并在计算机上找到了有用的信息。现在，我们可以向前迈进了。"
	"Continue working on destroying the portals from which these filthy creatures emerge"	"继续摧毁这些肮脏生物出现的入口"
	"The door panel leading to the main hall was broken by those creatures. We need to find a way to fix it"	"通往大厅的门板被那些生物打破了。”我们需要想办法解决它。"
	"Great, we've acquired a welding machine. Now we can try to repair the panel"	"太好了，我们得到了一台焊枪。现在我们可以尝试修复面板了。"
	"An identical panel was in the neighboring room. This might come in handy"	"一个相同的面板在邻近的房间里。这可能会派上用场。"
	"We'll have to put in some effort to push the panel to the door we need, leading to the main hall"	"我们得花点力气把门板推到我们需要的那扇门上，那扇门通向大厅。"
	"On the creatures' computer, we found materials about the explosives in the safe, along with the code — 666. However, one of the two buttons that need to be pressed simultaneously is broken"	"在这些生物的电脑上，我们在保险箱里找到了有关炸药的资料，还有密码- 666。但是，需要同时按下的两个按钮之一坏了。"
	"Now, we have everything necessary to destroy the main portal in the hall named 'Oblivion' and get out of here"	"现在，我们有了一切必要的东西来摧毁‘湮灭’大厅的主传送门，然后离开这里。"
}
}
