"lang" 
{ 
"Language" "Japanese" 
"Tokens" 
{
	"Prepare for the upcoming battle against the creatures and scout the unfamiliar terrain"	"迫り来るクリーチャーとの戦いに備え、この未知の地形を探索する"
	"Prevent the teleportation of hellish creatures and destroy all the portals in their lair"	"地獄のクリーチャーのテレポートを阻止し、これらの怪物の巣窟にあるすべてのポータルを破壊する"
	"The security system has been activated. The doors are locked. We need to find a way to unlock them"	"セキュリティシステムが作動しました — ドアがロックされています。解除する方法を見つける必要があります"
	"We managed to unlock the doors and found useful information on the computers. Now, we can move forward"	"ドアのロックを解除することに成功し、さらにコンピューターで有用な情報を見つけました。これで先に進めます"
	"Continue working on destroying the portals from which these filthy creatures emerge"	"これらの汚れたクリーチャーが湧き出るポータルの破壊を続ける"
	"The door panel leading to the main hall was broken by those creatures. We need to find a way to fix it"	"メインホールに通じるドアのパネルがクリーチャーによって壊されました。修理する方法を見つけなければなりません"
	"Great, we've acquired a welding machine. Now we can try to repair the panel"	"素晴らしい、溶接機を手に入れました。これでパネルの修理を試みることができます"
	"An identical panel was in the neighboring room. This might come in handy"	"隣の部屋に同じパネルがあります。これは役に立つかもしれません"
	"We'll have to put in some effort to push the panel to the door we need, leading to the main hall"	"このパネルをメインホールに通じるドアまで押すのは一苦労ですが、やらなければなりません"
	"On the creatures' computer, we found materials about the explosives in the safe, along with the code — 666. However, one of the two buttons that need to be pressed simultaneously is broken"	"クリーチャーのコンピューターで、金庫にある爆薬の資料とコード — 666 を見つけました。ただし、同時に押さなければならない2つのボタンのうち1つが壊れています"
	"Now, we have everything necessary to destroy the main portal in the hall named 'Oblivion' and get out of here"	"これで「オブリビオン」と呼ばれるホールのメインポータルを破壊し、ここから脱出するためのすべての準備が整いました"
}
}
